(Bernadette:)Raj, your tag's sticking out.
Thank you. That's the closest
I've come to sex in, like, two years.
(Bernadette:)Now I feel a little gross.
(Raj:)You're only making it seem
more real for me.
(Howard:)Hey, that's my wife.
(Howard:)If anyone's gonna make her feel
gross about sex, it's me.
(Raj:)Can we please talk about something
other than my depressing love life?
(Sheldon:)How about Penny's
depressing acting career?
Hey. it's been a little tough,
but Penny's following her dreams,
(Leonard:)and in my book,
that is not depressing.
(Penny:)Aw, thank you.
(Howard:)Is that book called
Lies l Tell to Get Sex?
(Raj:)Is that a real book?
I would totally read that book.
(Amy:)Can I borrow it when you're done?
(Penny:)Well, I'll have you guys know
(Penny:)I turned down a part
in a movie last week.
(Leonard:)Why would you do that?
(Penny:)Because it was crap.
It was a sequel to that awful
killer gorilla movie I was in.
(Bernadette:)Serial Ape-ist?
(Bernadette:)I thought you died in that.
(Sheldon:)She does. 42 minutes in.
(Raj:)While showering topless,
16 minutes after brief side butt
(Raj:)during a pillow fight
with her sorority sisters.
(Sheldon:)I have an eidetic memory.
I don't know what his problem is.
(Penny:)Okay, well, there are no
shower scenes in this one.
(Penny:)They just try to clone me
from my corpse,
(Penny:)but my DNA gets mixed
with the ape's DNA
(Penny:)and I end up running around
with giant gorilla hands and feet.
(Sheldon:)Am I missing something, or isn't that
the part she was born to play?